Switch ideas
Each player receives 7 cards
Up to two players
Four sets of cards
No jokers
Last card rule.
If you cannot place a card, you must pick up a card
Game cannot be won on a power card
Power cards:
	-Ace – Player can change suit if they wish, can be placed on any card of the same suit
	-Two – Next player must put down a two, or they must pick up two cards. These stack up if the next player does in fact play a two. For example, if three twos are played in a row, the next player must play a two or they will have to pick up six cards
	-Seven – You can play every card in the same suit as the seven. 
	-Eight – The next player must play an eight, or they will miss their turn.
	-Jack – Switch direction of play
If you have multiple of one number in different suits you can play them all at once


UI requirements
Need to show only the current player’s deck.
Need to show the last played card
Take in the names of each player
UI elements for showing the decks
UI elements for power cards
Power cards with indicators and descriptions
Hints and Tutorials


